<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Oken Lab</title>
    <link>https://okenk.github.io/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Oken Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://okenk.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://okenk.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://okenk.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;biography&#34;&gt;Biography&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kiva completed her BA in Math at Carleton College in 2010 and her PhD at the University of Washington in the Quantitative Ecology &amp;amp; Resource Management (QERM) program in 2016, followed by postdocs at Rutgers University and the University of Washington/NOAA Northwest Fisheries Science Center. Her research approach combines novel statistical methods and mechanistic mathematical models in order to study complex data sets, answer ecological questions, and help improve fisheries management. She&amp;rsquo;s also easily distracted by colleagues&amp;rsquo; statistical quandries. When not writing beautiful R code, she enjoys eating good food with friends and propelling herself in a variety of modes over trails, roads, rocks, water, and snow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://okenk.github.io/authors/andrea-odell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://okenk.github.io/authors/andrea-odell/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;biography&#34;&gt;Biography&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andrea is a first year PhD student in the Graduate Group in Ecology and a Sustainable Oceans NRT Trainee. She earned her BS in Aquatic and Fishery Sciences from the University of Washington in 2018 and worked as a lab technician at Scripps Institution of Oceanography before coming to Davis. Through her research, she seeks to better understand the ecological shifts that exploited fish populations and communities may experience in a rapidly changing environment and how these changes may introduce them to new fishing pressures. Outside of the lab, she is typically found outside playing soccer or volleyball, checking out the food scene, or exploring new places.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://okenk.github.io/authors/nima-farchadi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://okenk.github.io/authors/nima-farchadi/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;biography&#34;&gt;Biography&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nima is a PhD student in the San Diego State University - University of California, Davis Joint Doctoral Program in Ecology. Nima completed his MSc in Marine Science at University of San Diego studying the spatiotemporal distribution and habitat preferences of blue and black marlin in the eastern Pacific Ocean. His PhD research focuses on characterizing the spatiotemporal distribution of fishing vessels and highly migratory species under climate change scenarios using species distribution models, remote sensing, and climate models. This research is part of a collaborative project with researchers from University of Washington, NOAA, and Gulf of Maine Research Institute, that is developing a dynamic ocean management tool (FaCeT) that will help support climate-ready and sustainable fisheries. When he isn&amp;rsquo;t behind his computer writing code, you can find him outside hiking, surfing, snorkeling, camping, or enjoying good food and movies with friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://okenk.github.io/authors/sophia-wassermann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://okenk.github.io/authors/sophia-wassermann/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;biography&#34;&gt;Biography&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sophia has been developing her quantitative skills alongside her interests in ecology and conservation from her BA in Environmental Studies from Vassar College to her PhD in Marine Science from NUI Galway, with stops along the way at the School for Field Studies in the Turks &amp;amp; Caicos Islands, a Fulbright student grant at the University of Iceland, and a MSc in Biodiversity &amp;amp; Conservation from Trinity College Dublin. Her research focuses on the intersection of fisheries and climate change, applying computational approaches including individual-based models to fisheries assessment and management. When away from the desk, she likes to spend as much time near the water as possible, along with cooking, baking, and knitting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kiva-oken</title>
      <link>https://okenk.github.io/authors/kiva-oken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://okenk.github.io/authors/kiva-oken/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
